<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<!-- @formatter:off -->
<properties>
	<entry key="GENERAL">**GENERAL HELP INFORMATION**

I can understand only one command at a time.
Commands are NOT case-sensitive, unless otherwise noted.
DO NOT send one message with multiple commands on separate lines.
DO send one message with one command, then another message, and so on.
DO read the help for the command you want to use. Sometimes, I can do multiple tasks within one command.

**==========**

To let me update your inventory, you may:
+ post screenshots of your inventory screen. For details, type:
```%s help screenshot```
+ use commands. For details, type:
```%s help update```

OPTIONAL: Send commands and/or screenshots via DM: __Use my @mention ID.__

OPTIONAL: When sending commands via DM, you may omit the `%s` prefix.

**==========**

I react to commands!
:white_check_mark: Success!
:x: Fail!

If a command has multiple tasks for me, it is possible for both reactions to appear on one message.

**==========**

For help with specific commands, type:
```%s help [command]```

__Commands__
```fix
config
userConfig```
```css
check
checkTypes
clear
credits
group
info
total
update
users```
```
ping
status
nativeStatus
shutdown```</entry>
	<!-- Key "GENERAL" is listed first, for obvious reasons. All remaining keys are listed in alphabetical order. -->
	<entry key="CHECK">**Check**

The *primary* purpose of the `check` command is to verify that I read your screenshots correctly.
The *secondary* purpose of the `check` command is to search the database for all information that matches a search term you specify.


**\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*
ATTENTION
\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\***
This is a complex command. This command gives two different types of output, depending on how you use it. In addition, the output of this command can be __VERY LONG__. Please take the time to understand the `check` command before you use it.

*In most cases, you should use `%s total` instead.*

**==========**

*Primary purpose*
Check all of your own inventory.
`%s check`

OUTPUT: a list of all resource types currently in your inventory list in my database, __plus__ the quantity you have on hand of each type, __plus__ how long ago you updated each resource type.

**==========**

*Primary purpose*
Check all of one other user's inventory.
`%s check [userName]`
__The `userName` must be spelled correctly.
The `userName` must be an exact match.__ For more information, type:
`%s help users`

OUTPUT: a list of all resource types currently in `userName`'s inventory list in my database, __plus__ the quantity `userName` has on hand of each type, __plus__ how long ago `userName` updated each resource type.

**==========**

*Primary purpose* **AND** *Secondary purpose*
Check all items, __anywhere__ in my database, that match a search term you specify.
__The `searchTerm` may appear *anywhere* in a name, and it is *not* case-sensitive.__
`%s check [searchTerm]`


OUTPUT (PART 1): a list of all users who currently have on hand any non-zero quantity of a resource type matching the `searchTerm`, __plus__ the quantity of that resource type each user has on hand, __plus__ how long ago each user updated that resource type, __plus__ the total quantity of that resource type currently held by the entire guild.

If more than one resource type matches `searchTerm`, I will show you OUTPUT (PART 1) __separately__ for __each__ matching resource type.
__Example__: `searchTerm` "alumin" will match Aluminium AND Aluminium Bar AND Aluminium Bottle.


OUTPUT (PART 2): a list of all resource types currently in the inventory list for a user whose `userName` contains the `searchTerm`, __plus__ the quantity that user has on hand of each type, __plus__ how long ago that user updated each resource type.
__This is identical to the output of `%s check [userName]`.__

If more than one `userName` contains `searchTerm`, I will show you OUTPUT (PART 2) __separately__ for __each__ such user.


**See also:**
+ `%s help screenshot`
+ `%s help total`
+ `%s help users`</entry>
	<entry key="CHECKTYPES">**CheckTypes**

The purpose of the `checkTypes` command is to display the items (or "types" of resources) I can recognise in screenshots and list in my database.

**==========**

Display all known item types, arranged in alphabetical order using the currently selected language.
```%s checkTypes```


**See also:**
+ `%s help userConfig`
+ `%s help screenshot`</entry>
	<entry key="CLEAR">**Clear**

The purpose of the `clear` command is to remove resources from the inventory list. You can do several different things with this command.

**==========**

Clear all of your own inventory.
__Use this command before uploading screenshots that update your *entire* inventory.__
```%s clear```

**==========**

Clear one resource from your own inventory.
```%s clear [resourceName]```

**==========**

Clear all of one other user's inventory.
```%s clear [userName]```
__The userName must be spelled correctly.__ For more information, type:
```%s help users```

**==========**

Clear the entire guild's inventory.
```%s clear all```


**See also:**
+ `%s help screenshot`
+ `%s help users`
+ `%s help update`</entry>
	<entry key="COMMANDS">**Available Commands**

`help`
`help [command]`

`check`
`checkTypes`
`clear`
`config`
`credits`
`group`
`info`
`nativeStatus`
`ping`
`shutdown`
`status`
`total`
`update`
`userConfig`
`users`</entry>
	<entry key="CONFIG">**Config**

The purpose of the `config` command is to display and configure global options--that is, options that apply to everyone in the guild at the same time.
For information about options that apply only to you, type:
```%s help userConfig```

**==========**

Display the current global settings.
```%s config```

**==========**

Tell me the language of the guild's screenshots.
```%s config set language [de, en, es, fr, it, pt]```
__Options configured with the `userConfig` command always take priority over global options.__

**==========**

After I read a screenshot, I can list the resources I found and the quantity of each.
Tell me whether or not you want me to list resources after reading screenshots.
```%s config set OCR_RESULT [on, off]```
__The default setting is "on".__

**==========**

After I read a screenshot, I can delete the screenshot from the message history.
Tell me whether or not you want me to delete screenshots after reading them.
```%s config set DELETE_PICTURE_MESSAGE [on, off]```
__The default setting is "off".__

**==========**

I cannot change the settings for PREFIX or CHANNEL. These can be changed only at Heroku's website.
For more information, please contact your guild's bot administrator.


**See also:**
+ `%s help userConfig`
+ `%s help screenshot`</entry>
	<entry key="CREDITS">This bot was created by BlackCraze, with help from Dangercrow and firewaran.
Greek translations by ThatGreekGuy.
Portuguese translations by Benur21.
Documentation assistance by PellaAndroid.

Codebase:
https://github.com/BlackCraze/GameResourceBot/

Discord server (for developers and users):
https://discord.gg/e77yjxj</entry>
	<entry key="GROUP">**Group**

The purpose of the `group` command is to display and manage groups of resources. Groups have many uses.

**==========**

Create one or more new groups.
```%s group create [groupName] [groupName] [groupName]...```
__Group names are case-sensitive.__

**==========**

Add one or more resources to one group that already exists.
```%s group add [groupName] "[resourceName]" "[resourceName]" "[resourceName]"...```
__Quotation marks are REQUIRED for any [resourceName] containing a space.__

**==========**

Remove one resource from one group.
```%s group remove [groupName] "[resourceName]"```

**==========**

Rename one group.
```%s group rename [currentName] [newName]```

**==========**

Delete one group.
```%s group delete [groupName]```

**==========**

List all groups and their resources.
```%s group list```
***OR***
```%s group```


**See also:**
+ `%s help total`</entry>
	<entry key="INFO">I am a little bot who helps you coordinate your Discord guild better! Specifically, I have been designed to assist guilds who play the mobile game "Deep Town".</entry>
	<entry key="NATIVESTATUS">**NativeStatus**

The purpose of the `nativeStatus` command is to display my native memory status. Developers sometimes find this information useful during a troubleshooting process.

**==========**

Display the native memory status.
```%s nativeStatus```


**See also:**
`%s help status`</entry>
	<entry key="PING">**Ping**

The purpose of the `ping` command is to check whether I am able to respond to your commands.

**==========**

Test my responsiveness.
```%s ping```</entry>
	<entry key="SCREENSHOT">**Uploading Screenshots**
IMPORTANT: __There is no `%s screenshot` command. This information is to assist you with the process of uploading screenshots to get the best results.__

**==========**

To update your inventory using screenshots:
1) Ensure your language setting matches the language of your screenshots. For details, type:
```%s help userConfig```

2) Use your preferred method to take screenshots of your inventory screen in the game.
+ Both the resource name and the amount must be clearly visible.
+ Android - recommended app: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shamanland.privatescreenshots

3) Keep all screenshots in their original size.
+ DO NOT CROP IMAGES!! My ability to read screenshots depends on seeing the full screen.

4) Save all screenshots as PNG files. (Hint: That probably happens automatically.) If you do not know the file type of your screenshots, then upload them, anyway. If they're not PNG files, I will tell you.

5) In your Discord app, go to my channel (or DM) and upload the images.

**==========**

Occasionally, you may want me to ignore a resource in your inventory. For example, you may be saving something that is needed to upgrade a building, making it unavailable for the guild to use.

There are two different ways to handle this situation.
__Method #1__: Before uploading the screenshot that shows the resource you want to keep, use a photo editor to edit the screenshot. Scribble over the resource to make it impossible for me to read it.
__Method #2__: Upload the unaltered screenshot. Then use a command to delete the resource. For details, type:
```%s help clear```

**==========**

__TIPS__
+ You may upload screenshots to update your entire inventory at once, or only part of your inventory.
+ When updating your inventory, I will __always__:
+ ADD each resource in your screenshots to your inventory list, unless the resource is already there from a previous update.
+ REPLACE the old amount of each resource with the new amount.
+ When updating your inventory, I will __never__ remove a resource from your inventory list.
+ Example:
__old inventory list__
coal 5,000
copper 10,000

__new screenshot__
coal 7,000
iron 12,000

__new inventory list__
coal 7,000
copper 10,000
iron 12,000

If all your copper were gone, your new inventory list would be inaccurate.
To prevent errors like this, send `%s clear` BEFORE updating your __entire__ inventory.


**See also:**
+ `%s help update`
+ `%s help clear`
+ `%s help check`
+ `%s help userConfig`</entry>
	<entry key="SHUTDOWN">**Shutdown**

The purpose of the `shutdown` command is to make me shut down and restart. This can be useful if you experience an OutOfMemoryError.

**==========**

Shut down and restart this app.
```%s shutdown```</entry>
	<entry key="STATUS">**Status**

The purpose of the `status` command is to display my Java memory status. Developers sometimes find this information useful during a troubleshooting process.

**==========**

Display the Java memory status.
```%s status```


**See also:**
`%s help nativeStatus`</entry>
	<entry key="TOTAL">**Total**

The purpose of the `total` command is to display the total amount of one or more resources currently held by __the entire guild__.

**==========**

Display total quantities of all resources currently on hand.
```%s total```

**==========**

Display total quantity of one resource currently on hand.
```%s total [resourceName]```

**==========**

Display total quantities of multiple resources with parts of their names in common.
__EXAMPLES__
```%s total polished```
**OR**
```%s total bar```
**OR**
You get the point.

**==========**

Display total quantities of all resources in one group.
```%s total [groupName]```


**See also:**
+ `%s help check`
+ `%s help group`</entry>
	<entry key="UPDATE">**Update**

The purpose of the `update` command is add resources to your inventory list, or to change the quantities of existing resources in your inventory list. You may use this command:
+ *instead* of uploading screenshots;
**OR**
+ *after* uploading screenshots (to make small changes).

**==========**

The `update` command will accept multiple resources at the same time, if desired.
```%s update [resourceName] [quantity] [resourceName] [quantity] [resourceName] [quantity]...```

**==========**

+ CORRECT: Listing resources and amounts one after another, each separated only by a space.
+ WRONG: Listing resources on separate lines within one message. USE [ENTER] ONLY ONCE!!
+ WRONG: Entering more than one command within one message. USE [ENTER] ONLY ONCE!!


**See also:**
+ `%s help screenshot`
+ `%s help clear`</entry>
	<entry key="USERCONFIG">**UserConfig**

The purpose of the `userConfig` command is to display and configure options that apply to a single user--namely, you.

**==========**

Display your current settings.
```%s userConfig```

**==========**

Tell me the language of your screenshots, if it is different from your guild's default setting.
I will respond to you in that same language (if I have learned it).
You must continue to type all commands to me in English.
```%s userConfig set language [de, en, es, fr, it, pt]```
__Options configured with the `userConfig` command always take priority over global options.__

**==========**

Tell me your type of device.
__Fixes most errors reading screenshots.__
```%s userConfig set device [ANDROID, IPHONE]```


**See also:**
+ `%s help config`
+ `%s help screenshot`</entry>
	<entry key="USERS">**Users**

The purpose of the `users` command is to display and manage the active users in your guild.

**==========**

Display a list of all active users, __plus__ the number of resources each user has in the database, __plus__ how long ago each user made their most recent update.
```%s users```

**==========**

Synchronise the list of users in my database with the list of current users on your Discord server.
I will delete from my database all users who no longer have access to the %s channel on your Discord server.
Then I will add to my database any new users who have access to the %s channel on your Discord server.
```%s users sync```

**See also:**
+ `%s help update`</entry>
</properties>
<!-- @formatter:on -->